# David Jay



djay8400@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/david-jay-06911a217



(210) 209-0264



https://github.com/Djay8400/react-portfolio-davidiav-20

# Summary

I have 6 months experience as a Full Stack Web Developer and have provided links to my portfolio of work projects. Before deciding to enter a career in coding, I owned and operated a small Residential inspection business since 2014, but with the recent events of 2020, business slowed down and I decided to pursue my life long dreams of working in coding.

# **Experience**



#### Full Stack Web Developer

Freelance

Sep 2021 - Present (5 months +)



### Inspector

Self-employed

Feb 2014 - Jul 2021 (7 years 6 months)

I built this company from the ground up and managed as many as 6 employees that ran the office and performed the inspections. I managed and trained the inspectors and HR. I created and implemented marketing strategies to gain new customers and led the overall business to completing over 1000 inspections.

#### **Education**



## The University of Texas at San Antonio

Full Stack Web Developer Coding Bootcamp Certification, Computer Science Jul 2021 - Jan 2022

## **Licenses & Certifications**



UTSA Full Stack Web Developer Certification - The University of Texas at San **Antonio** 

#### Skills

Customer-focused Service • Technology Solutions • Project Management • JavaScript • Node.js • Bootstrap • MySQL • React.js • NoSQL • MERN Stack